title: MCU (Medium)
category: Marvel Universe

questions:
  - prompt: "Who was the first Avenger chronologically in the MCU timeline?"
    answers: ["Captain America"]

  - prompt: "Which Marvel hero was a surgeon before becoming a superhero?"
    answers: ["Doctor Strange", "Dr Strange"]

  - prompt: "Who was the villain in Black Panther?"
    answers: ["Killmonger"]

  - prompt: "Which Infinity Stone was in Loki’s scepter?"
    answers: ["Mind Stone"]

  - prompt: "What is the name of Peter Quill's father?"
    answers: ["Ego"]

  - prompt: "Which Avenger can shrink and grow in size?"
    answers: ["Ant-Man", "Ant Man"]

  - prompt: "What’s the name of Thor’s sister in Ragnarok?"
    answers: ["Hela"]

  - prompt: "What alien race invaded New York in the first Avengers movie?"
    answers: ["Chitauri"]

  - prompt: "Who destroyed Tony Stark’s house in Iron Man 3?"
    answers: ["The Mandarin"]

  - prompt: "What group is led by Nick Fury?"
    answers: ["S.H.I.E.L.D.", "SHIELD"]

